Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2
- Box: 4, Folder: 64, Publication (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Item 1: Connecticut General Suggestion Plan, Publication (Box 4, Folder 64)
    Author: Connecticut General Life Insurance Co.
  - Item 2: You and an Idea, 1953; Publication (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Item 3: Suggestion System, Publication (Box 4, Folder 64)
- Box: 4, Folder: 65, Publication (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Item 1: Skills for the Future, 1958; Publication (Box 4, Folder 65)
    Author: Connecticut Labor Department
- Box: 4, Folder: 66, Publication (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Item 1: Connecticut Municipal Employee's Retirement Fund, Publication (Box 4, Folder 66)
    Author: Connecticut Municipal Employee's Retirement Fund
- Box: 4, Folder: 67, Publication (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Item 1: Library Bulletin, 1972; Publication (Box 4, Folder 67)
    Author: Consolidated Edison Company
- Box: 4, Folder: 68, Publication (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Item 1: You and Conolidated, Publication (Box 4, Folder 68)
    Author: Consolidated Electrodynamics Corp.
- Box: 4, Folder: 69, Publication (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Item 1: Index, Publication (Box 4, Folder 69)
    Author: Construction Industry Employees Association
- Box: 4, Folder: 70, Publication (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Item 1: Construction Industry Joint Conference, 1958; Publication (Box 4, Folder 70)
    Author: Construction Industry Joint Conference
    Notes: April 7
  - Item 2: Maintiaining Production for America, Publication (Box 4, Folder 70)
- Box: 4, Folder: 71, Publication (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - Item 1: An Analyis of Proposals to Cure Juvenile Delinquency by Lowering Child Labor Standards, 1955; Publication (Box 4, Folder 71)
    Author: Consumers League of New Jersey
  - Item 2: New Jersey Consumer Protection Laws, 1964; Publication (Box 4, Folder 71)
- Box: 4, Folder: 72, Publication (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - Item 1: End Feudalism on the Farms, Publication (Box 4, Folder 72)
    Author: Consumers League of New York
  - Item 2: Ad Hoc Conference on Migrant Farm Labor, 1958; Publication (Box 4, Folder 72)
- Box: 4, Folder: 73, Publication (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - Item 1: Group Insurance Plan, 1965; Publication (Box 4, Folder 73)
    Author: Container Corporation of America
  - Item 2: Retirement Plan, 1957; Publication (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - Item 3: Group Insurance Plan, 1967; Publication (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - Item 4: Retirement Plan, 1964; Publication (Box 4, Folder 73)
- Box: 4, Folder: 74, Publication (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - Item 1: Continental Can Company, Publication (Box 4, Folder 74)
    Author: Continental Can Company
- Box: 5, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Inside, 1977; Publication (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Author: Consumer's Power Company
    Notes: Vol. 3, No. 9 April 29
  - Item 2: Inside, 1977; Publication (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Notes: Vol. 3, no. 8 April 15
  - Item 3: Inside, 1977; Publication (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Notes: Vol. 3, No. 6 March 18
  - Item 4: Inside, 1977; Publication (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Notes: Vol. 3, No. 5 March 4
  - Item 5: Inside, 1976; Publication (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Notes: Vol. 2, No. 20 Dec. 3
  - Item 6: Inside, 1976; Publication (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Notes: Vol. 2, No. 19 Nov. 19
  - Item 7: Inside Vol. 2, No. 10 July 16, 1976; Publication (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Inside, 1976; Publication (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Notes: Vol. 2, No. 18 Nov. 5
  - Item 9: Consumer Power Employees' News, Publication (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Notes: Vol. 4, No. 4
  - Item 10: Headline News Review, 1976; Publication (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Notes: July 23
  - Item 11: Retireline, Publication (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: Inside, 1977; Publication (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Notes: vol. 3, No. 14 July 8
  - Item 13: Inside, 1977; Publication (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Notes: Vol. 3, No. 17 Aug. 19
  - Item 14: Inside, 1977; Publication (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Notes: Vol. 3, No. 18 Sept. 2
  - Item 15: Inside, 1977; Publication (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Notes: Vol. 3, No. 21 Oct. 14
  - Item 16: Inside, 1978; Publication (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Notes: Vol. 4, No. 1 Jan. 6
  - Item 17: Inside, 1978; Publication (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Notes: Vol. 4, No. 2 Jan. 20
  - Item 18: Executive Administrative and Professional Employees, 1976; Publication (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Item 19: Inside, 1978; Publication (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Notes: Vol. 4, No.6 March 17
  - Item 20: Salaried Employees-Weekly, 1976; Publication (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Item 21: The President's Letter, 1976; Publication (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Item 22: Inside, 1978; Publication (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Notes: Vol. 4, No. 12 June 9
  - Item 23: Inside, 1978; Publication (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Notes: Vol. 4, No. 14 July 21
  - Item 24: Inside, 1978; Publication (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Notes: Vol. 4, No. 11 May 26
  - Item 25: Inside, 1978; Publication (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Notes: Vol. 4, No. 10 May 12
  - Item 26: Inside, 1978; Publication (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Notes: Vol. 4, No. 8 April 14
  - Item 27: Inside, 1978; Publication (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Notes: Vol. 4, No. 13 June 23
  - Item 28: Inside, 1978; Publication (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Notes: Vol. 4, No. 15 Aug. 4
  - Item 29: Inside, 1978; Publication (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Notes: Vol. 4, No. 20 Oct. 13
  - Item 30: CP News, 1979; Publication (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Notes: April 5
- Box: 5, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: CP News, 1979; Publication (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Notes: Vol. 1, No. 7 April 13
  - Item 2: CP News, 1979; Publication (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Notes: Vol. 1, No. 6 March 30
  - Item 3: Consumer's Power Company Letter, 1979; Publication (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Notes: April 2
  - Item 4: CP News, 1979; Publication (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Notes: Vol. 1, No. 5 March 16
  - Item 5: CP News, 1979; Publication (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Notes: Vol. 1, No. 1 January 19
  - Item 6: Inside, 1978; Publication (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Notes: Vol. 4, No. 13 Dec. 8
  - Item 7: CP News, 1979; Publication (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Notes: Vol. 1, No. 8 April 27
  - Item 8: CP News, 1979; Publication (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Notes: Vol. 1, No. 2 Feb. 2
  - Item 9: CP News, 1979; Publication (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Notes: Vol. 1, No. 3 February 16
  - Item 10: CP News, 1979; Publication (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Notes: Vol. 1, No.9 May 11
  - Item 11: CP News, 1979; Publication (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Notes: Vol. 1, No. 10 May 25
  - Item 12: Fundamentals of Basic Electricity Panels, 1964; Publication (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Author: R.J. Cleaver: E.J. Meeusen: R.A. Wells
- Box: 5, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Social Action, 1938; Publication (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Author: Louis Stark
    Notes: Aug. 15, 1938
  - Item 2: To Tell the Truth, Publication (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Author: Consumer's Union of the U.S. Inc.
  - Item 3: Consumer Reports, 1956; Publication (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Box: 5, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Newsbulletin, 1976; Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Author: Continental Insurance Company
    Notes: Vol. 2, No. 4 Aug.
  - Item 2: Continental People, 1979; Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Notes: Vol. 2, No. 7 July
  - Item 3: The Courier, 1979; Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Notes: Vol. 5, No. 4 Aug.
  - Item 4: Newsbulletin, 1976; Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: The Courier, 1977; Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Notes: Vol. 3, No. 6 Dec.
  - Item 6: Continental People, 1978; Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Notes: Vol. 1 ,No. 4 May
  - Item 7: Continental People, 1978; Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Notes: Vol. 1, No. 6 July
  - Item 8: The Courier, 1978; Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Notes: Vol. 4, No. 3 June
  - Item 9: Bulletin, 1978; Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Item 10: The Courier, 1978; Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Notes: Vol. 4, No. 4 Aug.
  - Item 11: The Courier, 1978; Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Notes: Vol. 4, No. 5 Oct.
  - Item 12: Continental People, 1979; Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Notes: Vol. 2, No. 1 Jan.
  - Item 13: Vol. 2, No. 3 March, 1979; Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Item 14: Vol. 2, No. 5 May, 1979; Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Item 15: The Courier, 1979; Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Notes: Vol. 5, No.5 June
  - Item 16: Continental People, 1979; Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Item 17: The Courier, 1979; Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Notes: Vol. 5, No. 5 Oct.
- Box: 5, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Welcome to the Conventional American Group, Publication (Box 5, Folder 5)
    Author: Conventional American Group
- Box: 5, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Quality Products Through Creative Enigineering, 1971; Publication (Box 5, Folder 6)
    Author: Continental Writ Electronics Corp.
- Box: 5, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: "Corn Products Refining": Half and Century of Progress and Leadership (1906-1958), Publication (Box 5, Folder 7)
    Author: W.T. Brady
  - Item 2: The Story of Corn and its Products, Publication (Box 5, Folder 7)
    Author: Corn Products Refining Company
- Box: 5, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: "In the Interest of General Welfare", Publication (Box 5, Folder 8)
    Author: Cornell University School of Industrial Labor Relations
  - Item 2: Questions for Discussion at Meeting of Directors of Industrial Relations Centers, 1967; Publication (Box 5, Folder 8)
    Author: Gerald Somers
    Notes: May 25-26
  - Item 3: Education for Mutual Respect, Publication (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Box: 5, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Report of the Commission on Teaching Assistants, 1968; Publication (Box 5, Folder 9)
    Author: Cornell University Commission on Teaching Assistants
    Notes: Dec. 16
  - Item 2: "Strike is Postponed While Talks Continue", 1969; Publication (Box 5, Folder 9)
    Notes: March 17
  - Item 3: "Research Assistants To Demand 'Parity'", 1969; Publication (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: Agreement Signed, 1970; Publication (Box 5, Folder 9)
    Notes: Dec. 17
  - Item 5: Meeting Set Tuesday, 1969; Publication (Box 5, Folder 9)
    Notes: Feb. 17
  - Item 6: "Grads Propose Minimum Scale", 1969; Publication (Box 5, Folder 9)
    Notes: Feb. 19
  - Item 7: "Strike Threats Continue", 1969; Publication (Box 5, Folder 9)
    Notes: March 11
  - Item 8: "Graduates Plan Halt for Week", 1969; Publication (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Box: 5, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Suggestion System, 1951; Publication (Box 5, Folder 10)
    Author: Corning Glass Works
  - Item 2: The Gaffer, 1977; Publication (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: The Gaffer, 1977; Publication (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Item 4: Key to the Office, 1969; Publication (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Box: 5, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Employee Magazine Ideas, Publication (Box 5, Folder 11)
    Author: Corn Products Company
- Box: 5, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Constitution and By-Laws, Publication (Box 5, Folder 12)
    Author: Corrective Officers Benevolent Association, Inc.
- Box: 5, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: A Case Study in Labour Force Recruitment and Training, 1965; Publication (Box 5, Folder 13)
    Author: Cosmos Imperial Mills
- Box: 5, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: It Depends on Consumer Competence Whether Competition Improves Quality or Debases It, Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
    Author: John Maurice clark
  - Item 2: Newsletter, 1967; Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
    Author: Council on Consumer Information
    Notes: Vol. 15, No. 2 Oct.
- Box: 5, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: The Meaning of the Council for Financial Aid to Education, Inc., 1955; Publication (Box 5, Folder 15)
    Author: Council for Financial Aid to Education
  - Item 2: Education is Everybody's Business, Publication (Box 5, Folder 15)
    Author: Frank W. Abrams
- Box: 5, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Constitution and By-Laws of the Council of Profit Sharing Industries, 1965; Publication (Box 5, Folder 16)
    Author: Council of Profit Sharing Industries
- Box: 5, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Commmunications Materials Available to You as a Member of Council of Profit Sharing Industries, Publication (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Box: 5, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Membership Roster, 1965; Publication (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Item 2: Profit Sharing, Publication (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Item 3: Roster Supplement, 1965; Publication (Box 5, Folder 18)
    Notes: Sept. 1, 1964- March 31, 1965
  - Item 4: Membership Roster, 1963; Publication (Box 5, Folder 18)
    Notes: June 1
  - 1963, Publication (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Item 6: Scope and Activities of the Council of Profit Sharing Industries, Publication (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Item 7: Sixth Annual Conference Program, 1953; Publication (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Item 8: Union Leader Corporation, 1957; Publication (Box 5, Folder 18)
    Author: William Loeb
  - Item 9: Fifth Annual Conference Program, 1952; Publication (Box 5, Folder 18)
    Notes: Nov. 6-7
  - Item 10: Seventh Annual Conference Program, 1954; Publication (Box 5, Folder 18)
    Notes: Oct. 28-29
  - Item 11: Declaratin of Principles and Constitution, Publication (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Item 12: Membership, 1955; Publication (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Item 13: Membership List, 1954; Publication (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Item 14: Membership List, 1953; Publication (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Item 15: Membership List, 1958; Publication (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Item 16: Report to the Membership on the State of our Council, 1960; Publication (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Item 17: Council of Profit Sharing Industries Letter, 1963; Publication (Box 5, Folder 18)
    Notes: Nov. 11
- Box: 5, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: The Senior Citizen, 1953; Publication (Box 5, Folder 19)
    Author: Council of Senior Citizens of Tompkins County
  - Item 2: The Senior Citizen, 1952; Publication (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Box: 5, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Social Action: Church-Labor Relations, 1944; Publication (Box 5, Folder 20)
    Author: Council for Social Action of the Congregational Christian Church
    Notes: Oct. 15, 1944
  - Item 2: Guiding Principles for Organized Labor and Management Relatinos, 1953; Publication (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Box: 5, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: The Legend of Packing, 1953; Publication (Box 5, Folder 21)
    Author: Crandall Packing Company
- Box: 5, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Suggestion System, Publication (Box 5, Folder 22)
    Author: Crane Company
- Box: 5, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Record, 1951; Publication (Box 5, Folder 23)
    Author: Craddock Terry Shoe Corp.
  - Item 2: Record, 1951; Publication (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Box: 5, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Crane World, 1956; Publication (Box 5, Folder 24)
    Author: Crane Co.
  - Item 2: Group Insurance for Our Employees, Publication (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Item 3: Pension Plan, Publication (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Item 4: How the Crane Companies' Pension Plan, 1960; Publication (Box 5, Folder 24)
    Notes: Oct. 1
  - Item 5: Chicago Works, 1953; Publication (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Item 6: Rules and Regulations, 1951; Publication (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Item 7: Bulletin of Wages, 1888; Publication (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Item 8: CC Welcomes to Crane Co., 1953; Publication (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Item 9: Centennial Crane World Issue, 1955; Publication (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Item 10: How to Promote a Know-Your-Company Contest, Publication (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Item 11: Crane World, 1955; Publication (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Item 12: Suggestin System, 1949; Publication (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Item 13: Annual Report, 1954; Publication (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Box: 5, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: A Request From the Creative Problem-Solving Institute, Publication (Box 5, Folder 25)
    Author: Creative Education Foundation
  - Item 2: The 10th Annual Creative Problem-Solving Institute, Publication (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Item 3: Developments in the Creative Education Movement, Publication (Box 5, Folder 25)
    Author: Alex F. Osborn
- Box: 5, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Report of Proceedings, 1962; Publication (Box 5, Folder 26)
    Author: Creative Problem-Solving Institute-University of Buffalo
    Notes: June 25-27
- Box: 5, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: The Credit Union Way, Publication (Box 5, Folder 27)
    Author: Credit Union National Association
  - Item 2: Credit Unions in Educational Groups, 1955; Publication (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Item 3: They Endorse All Credit Unions, 1955; Publication (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Item 4: The Credit Union Yearbook, 1956; Publication (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Item 5: The Credit Union Yearbook, 1957; Publication (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Item 6: Bibliography, 1066; Publication (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Item 7: What Are Credit Unions and How Can We Use Them, Publication (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Box: 5, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Publication (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Item 2: The Credit Union Yearbook, 1954; Publication (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Item 3: International Credit Union Yearbook, 1964; Publication (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Box: 5, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: A Guide to Your Employee Benefits, 1972; Publication (Box 5, Folder 29)
    Author: Creole Petroleum Corporation
- Box: 5, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Wage and Salary: Training Course for Supervisors, 1957; Publication (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Item 2: Annual Report, 1953; Publication (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Box: 5, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Organization and Planning, Publication (Box 5, Folder 31)
    Author: Cresap, McCormick & Paget
- Box: 5, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Introduction to Crocker-Anglo Bank, Publication (Box 5, Folder 32)
    Author: Crocker-Anglo Bank
- Box: 5, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: That You May Always Remember Crossett, Publication (Box 5, Folder 33)
    Author: Crosset Co.
- Box: 5, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Steps to Settling a Grievance, 1959; Publication (Box 5, Folder 34)
    Author: Crouse Hinds Company
- Box: 5, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Bulletin 2591, Publication (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Item 2: Spans Four Fields in the Electrical Industry, Publication (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Item 3: Family Circle: Organization Charts of the Crouse-Hinds Company, 1958; Publication (Box 5, Folder 35)
- Box: 5, Folder: 36, Publication (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: News, 1976; Publication (Box 5, Folder 36)
    Notes: May- June
  - Item 2: News, 1976; Publication (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Item 3: News, 1976; Publication (Box 5, Folder 36)
    Notes: Jan.- Feb.
  - Item 4: News, 1976; Publication (Box 5, Folder 36)
    Notes: Nov.- Dec.
- Box: 5, Folder: 37, Publication (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: Welcome, Publication (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Item 2: You and Crouse-Hinds, 1962; Publication (Box 5, Folder 37)
- Box: 5, Folder: 38, Publication (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: Major Medical Insurance, Publication (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Item 2: Group Insurance Plan, 1953; Publication (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Item 3: Take a Look at tomorrow with the Crouse Hinds Retirement Income Plan, Publication (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Item 4: Retirement Income Plan of Crouse Hinds Company, 1953; Publication (Box 5, Folder 38)
- Box: 5, Folder: 39, Publication (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: Principles of Personnel Administration, 1960; Publication (Box 5, Folder 39)
    Notes: March 7
  - Item 2: Service Award Plan, Publication (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Item 3: So you're Going to Move, Publication (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Item 4: So you're Going to Move: For Married Employees, Publication (Box 5, Folder 39)
- Box: 5, Folder: 40, Publication (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: Employee Security Program, Publication (Box 5, Folder 40)
    Author: Crown Central Petroleum Corporation
- Box: 5, Folder: 41, Publication (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: Employees' Annual Report, Publication (Box 5, Folder 41)
    Author: Crown Cork and Seal Company, Inc.
  - Item 2: Annual Report, 1953; Publication (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Item 3: The Crown Corker, 1954; Publication (Box 5, Folder 41)
- Box: 5, Folder: 42, Publication (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: Crown's Diamond Anniversary, 1952; Publication (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Item 2: Group Insurance Plan, 1953; Publication (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Item 3: Your Retirement Income Plan, 1954; Publication (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Item 4: Wage and Salary Administratin Handbook, 1953; Publication (Box 5, Folder 42)
- Box: 5, Folder: 43, Publication (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Item 1: Your Suggestion Plan, Publication (Box 5, Folder 43)
    Author: Crown Zellerbach Corp.
- Box: 5, Folder: 44, Publication (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Item 1: Pulp, Paper and Pioneers-The Story of Crown Zellerbach Corp., Publication (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Item 2: Profile: Crown Zellerbach, Publication (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Item 3: Pulp, Paper and Pioneers, 1961; Publication (Box 5, Folder 44)
    Author: R.O. Hunt
  - Item 4: Growing Paper on Tree Farms, Publication (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Item 5: Years of Paper, 1952; Publication (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Item 6: Papermaking at Antioch, 1957; Publication (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Item 7: Crown Zellerbach Building, Publication (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Item 8: Partners in Industry, Publication (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Item 9: Job Introduction for New Employee, Publication (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Item 10: You and Your Retirement Plan, 1959; Publication (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Item 11: Rules and Customs, Publication (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Item 12: You and Your Welfare Plan, Publication (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Item 13: Retirement Plan, 1951; Publication (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Item 14: Retirement Plan, 1961; Publication (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Item 15: Retirement Plan/Annual Report, 1960; Publication (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Item 16: A Plan of Group Insurance for Salaried Employees, 1957; Publication (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Item 17: A Plan of Group Insurance for Hourly Employees, 1957; Publication (Box 5, Folder 44)
- Box: 5, Folder: 45, Publication (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Item 1: Management Digest, 1951; Publication (Box 5, Folder 45)
    Notes: Number 87 June 20
  - Item 2: Management Digest, 1951; Publication (Box 5, Folder 45)
    Notes: Number 89 July 30
  - Item 3: Management Digest, 1951; Publication (Box 5, Folder 45)
    Notes: Number 91 Aug. 16
  - Item 4: Management Digest, 1952; Publication (Box 5, Folder 45)
    Notes: Number 109 May 16
  - Item 5: Management Digest, 1952; Publication (Box 5, Folder 45)
    Notes: Number 113 July 22
  - Item 6: Management Digest, 1953; Publication (Box 5, Folder 45)
    Notes: Number 126
  - Item 7: Crown Zellerbach Times, 1961; Publication (Box 5, Folder 45)
    Notes: Vol. 2, No. 3 March
  - Item 8: Crown Zellerbach Times, 1961; Publication (Box 5, Folder 45)
    Notes: Vol. 2, No. 10 October
  - Item 9: Crown Zellerbach Corp. Annual Report, 1966; Publication (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Item 10: Annual Report, 1960; Publication (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Item 11: Annual Report, 1952; Publication (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Item 12: Annual Report, 1964; Publication (Box 5, Folder 45)
- Box: 5, Folder: 46, Publication (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Item 1: Here it is! Good Ideas Mean Money for You: The Crucible Suggestion Plan, Publication (Box 5, Folder 46)
    Author: Crucible Steel
  - Item 2: The Suggestion Plan Manual, 1956; Publication (Box 5, Folder 46)